KEANU BOWKER

CONTACT

0614990030 0676003506 keanubowker8@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

Junior data scientist with a creative edge. I always strive to achieve the highest standard in any situation. I find working on new challenges and learning new things alluring, as I have a very curious mind. Experienced in executing data-driven solutions to increase the efficiency of business operations.

EDUCATION

UMUZI ACADEMY

2019 - 2020 | National Certificate in Information Technology(Systems Development)

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST UMUZI 2020-12-7 - CURRENT

- Data Cleaning and Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Machine Learning

BUSINESS INTELLIGENCE ANALYST INTERN

INVESTEC SPECIALIST BANK

2020-03-16 - 2020-06-15

- Compile Power BI dashboards
- Data mining
- Data engineering

JUNIOR DATA SCIENTIST

UMUZI

2019-06-7 - 2020-03-12

- Data Cleaning and Analysis
- Data Visualization
- Machine Learning

COMMERCIAL VETTING

NEDBANK INSURANCE

2019-03-01 - 2019-06-01

- Contact client's
- Update details

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT LEARNERSHIP

JOHANESSBURG CENTRE FOR SOFTWARE ENGINEERING 2018-03-01 - 2019-02-01

• Learnt basic IT and Software Concepts

SKILLS

Python, Machine Learning, SQL Human Centered Design, Data Visualization, Data Analysis, Excel, Data Manipulation, Data Modelling, Google Data Studio, Power BI